Guide to the Joint Western Area Committee Records, 1965-2004 LAC0003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- JWAC February 1984 [7/28], 1984 February (Box 89, Folder 4)
  O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries), Minutes Meeting February 13-17, 1984, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1984 [8/28], 1984 February (Box 89, Folder 5)
  Break Bulk Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1984 [9/28], 1984 February (Box 89, Folder 6)
  Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Break Bulk Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1984 [10/28], 1984 February (Box 90, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1984 [11/28], 1984 February (Box 90, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1984 [12/28], 1984 February (Box 90, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1984 [13/28], 1984 February (Box 90, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1984 [14/28], 1984 February (Box 90, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1984 [15/28], 1984 February (Box 90, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1984 [16/28], 1984 February (Box 90, Folder 7)
- JWAC February 1984 [17/28], 1984 February (Box 91, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1984 [18/28], 1984 February (Box 91, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1984 [19/28], 1984 February (Box 91, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1984 [20/28], 1984 February (Box 91, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1984 [21/28], 1984 February (Box 91, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1984 [22/28], 1984 February (Box 91, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1984 [23/28], 1984 February (Box 92, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1984 [24/28], 1984 February (Box 92, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1984 [25/28], 1984 February (Box 92, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1984 [26/28], 1984 February (Box 92, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Warning Letters
- JWAC February 1984 [27/28], 1984 February (Box 92, Folder 5)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Warning Letters
- JWAC February 1984 [28/28], 1984 February (Box 92, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1984 [1/26], 1984 May (Box 93, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting May 14-18, 1984, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee of Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1984 [2/26], 1984 May (Box 93, Folder 2)
  O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1984 [3/26], 1984 May (Box 93, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting May 14-18, 1984, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1984 [4/26], 1984 May (Box 93, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1984 [5/26], 1984 May (Box 93, Folder 5)
  Agenda, minutes meeting May 14-18, 1984, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1984 [6/26], 1984 May (Box 93, Folder 6)
  Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee, O-T-R Disputes, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (summaries)
- JWAC May 1984 [6/26], 1984 May (Box 93, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1984 [7/26], 1984 May (Box 94, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting May 14-18, 1984, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1984 [8/26], 1984 May (Box 94, Folder 2)
  Minutes Meeting May 14-18, 1984, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1984 [9/26], 1984 May (Box 94, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1984 [10/26], 1984 May (Box 94, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1984 [11/26], 1984 May (Box 94, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1984 [12/26], 1984 May (Box 95, Folder 1)
  95-1, 12/26, Proceedings/Transcripts of the Main Committee
- JWAC May 1984 [13/26], 1984 May (Box 95, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1984 [14/26], 1984 May (Box 95, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1984 [15/26], 1984 May (Box 95, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1984 [16/26], 1984 May (Box 95, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1984 [17/26], 1984 May (Box 95, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1984 [18/26], 1984 May (Box 95, Folder 7)
- JWAC May 1984 [19/26], 1984 May (Box 96, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1984 [20/26], 1984 May (Box 96, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1984 [21/26], 1984 May (Box 96, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1984 [22/26], 1984 May (Box 96, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1984 [23/26], 1984 May (Box 96, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1984 [24/26], 1984 May (Box 96, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1984 [25/26], 1984 May (Box 97, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1984 [25/26], 1984 May (Box 97, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1984 [26/26], 1984 May (Box 97, Folder 2)
- JWAC June 1984 [1/4], 1984 June (Box 97, Folder 3)
- JWAC June 1984 [2/4], 1984 June (Box 97, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Main Committee, supplemental documentation for committee hearing
- JWAC June 1984 [3/4], 1984 June (Box 97, Folder 5)
  Supplemental documentation for committee hearing
- JWAC June 1984 [4/4], 1984 June (Box 97, Folder 6)
- JWAC July 1984 [1/1], 1984 July (Box 98, Folder 1)
  JWAC Rider Committee Meeting Minutes
- JWAC August 1984 [1/17], 1984 August (Box 98, Folder 2)
  Agenda, Minutes, Meeting August 13-17, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee Local Operations and Office Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, Joint Council #7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1984 [2/17], 1984 August (Box 98, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting August 13-17, 1984, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee Local Operations and Office Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1984 [3/17], 1984 August (Box 98, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1984 [4/17], 1984 August (Box 98, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1984 [5/17], 1984 August (Box 98, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1984 [6/17], 1984 August (Box 98, Folder 7)
- JWAC August 1984 [7/17], 1984 August (Box 99, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1984 [8/17], 1984 August (Box 99, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1984 [9/17], 1984 August (Box 99, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1984 [10/17], 1984 August (Box 99, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the O-T-R and Automotive Committee
- JWAC August 1984 [11/17], 1984 August (Box 99, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1984 [12/17], 1984 August (Box 99, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1984 [13/17], 1984 August (Box 100, Folder 1)
  Transcripts/Proceedings at the BreakBulk Committee
- JWAC August 1984 [14/17], 1984 August (Box 100, Folder 2)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Committee for Local Operations
- JWAC August 1984 [15/17], 1984 August (Box 100, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1984 [16/17], 1984 August (Box 100, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1984 [17/17], 1984 August (Box 100, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1984 [1/18], 1984 November (Box 100, Folder 6)
  Agenda Meeting November 5-9, 1984, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee Local Operations-Office Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Discharges, Terminations &Suspensions, Warning letters, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1984 [2/18], 1984 November (Box 101, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting November 5-9, 1984, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee Local Operations-Office Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Discharges, Terminations &Suspensions, Warning Letters, Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1984 [3/18], 1984 November (Box 101, Folder 2)
  Agenda Meeting November 5-9, 1984, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee Local Operations-Office Disputes, Discharges, Terminations &Suspensions, Warning Letters, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1984 [4/18], 1984 November (Box 101, Folder 3)
  Transcript of the Meeting of Union Members, JWAC, and Representatives of Local Unions, November 5, 1984, Transcript/Proceedings of the Joint Session of the Full and Main Committee
- JWAC November 1984 [5/18], 1984 November (Box 101, Folder 4)
  Transcript/Proceedings of the Main Committee
- JWAC November 1984 [6/18], 1984 November (Box 101, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1984 [7/18], 1984 November (Box 101, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1984 [8/18], 1984 November (Box 102, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1984 [9/18], 1984 November (Box 102, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1984 [10/18], 1984 November (Box 102, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1984 [11/18], 1984 November (Box 102, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1984 [12/18], 1984 November (Box 102, Folder 5)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Break Bulk Committee
- JWAC November 1984 [13/18], 1984 November (Box 102, Folder 6)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Local Operations--Office Disputes Committee
- JWAC November 1984 [14/18], 1984 November (Box 103, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1984 [15/18], 1984 November (Box 103, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1984 [16/18], 1984 November (Box 103, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1984 [17/18], 1984 November (Box 103, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations &Suspensions, Warning Letters
- JWAC November 1984 [18/18], 1984 November (Box 103, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1985 [1/15], 1985 February (Box 103, Folder 6)
  Agenda, Minutes February 11-15, 1985, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Local Operations and Office Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations &Suspensions, Warning Letters, Break Bulk Committee, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC February 1985 [2/15], 1985 February (Box 104, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1985 [3/15], 1985 February (Box 104, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1985 [4/15], 1985 February (Box 104, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1985 [5/15], 1985 February (Box 104, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1985 [6/15], 1985 February (Box 104, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1985 [7/15], 1985 February (Box 104, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1985 [6/25], 1985 February (Box 104, Folder 7)
  105-1, 8/15, Proceedings/Transcripts of the OTR & Automotive Committee
- JWAC February 1985 [8/15], 1985 February (Box 105, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the OTR & Automotive Committee
- JWAC February 1985 [9/15], 1985 February (Box 105, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1985 [10/15], 1985 February (Box 105, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1985 [11/15], 1985 February (Box 105, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Local Operations & Office Committee
- JWAC February 1985 [12/15], 1985 February (Box 105, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1985 [13/15], 1985 February (Box 105, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1985 [14/15], 1985 February (Box 106, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations &Suspensions, Warning Letters
- JWAC February 1985 [15/15], 1985 February (Box 106, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1985 [1/16], 1985 May (Box 106, Folder 3)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting May 13-17, 1985, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations & Office, Break Bulk Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters; Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1985 [2/16], 1985 May (Box 106, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1985 [3/16], 1985 May (Box 106, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1985 [4/16], 1985 May (Box 106, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1985 [5/16], 1985 May (Box 107, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1985 [6/16], 1985 May (Box 107, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1985 [7/16], 1985 May (Box 107, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1985 [8/16], 1985 May (Box 107, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Break Bulk Committee
- JWAC May 1985 [9/16], 1985 May (Box 107, Folder 5)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Over-the-Road Committee
- JWAC May 1985 [10/16], 1985 May (Box 107, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1985 [11/16], 1985 May (Box 108, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Local Operations and Office Committee
- JWAC May 1985 [12/16], 1985 May (Box 108, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1985 [13/16], 1985 May (Box 108, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1985 [14/16], 1985 May (Box 108, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1985 [15/16], 1985 May (Box 108, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1985 [16/16], 1985 May (Box 108, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1985 [1/14], 1985 August (Box 109, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting August 1985, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations & Office, Break Bulk Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters; Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1985 [2/14], 1985 August (Box 109, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1985 [3/14], 1985 August (Box 109, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1985 [4/14], 1985 August (Box 109, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1985 [5/14], 1985 August (Box 109, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1985 [6/14], 1985 August (Box 109, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1985 [7/14], 1985 August (Box 110, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Over-The-Road Committee
- JWAC August 1985 [8/14], 1985 August (Box 110, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1985 [9/14], 1985 August (Box 110, Folder 3)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Local Operations, Office, Break Bulk Committees
- JWAC August 1985 [10/14], 1985 August (Box 110, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1985 [11/14], 1985 August (Box 110, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1985 [12/14], 1985 August (Box 110, Folder 6)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Discharge Committee
- JWAC August 1985 [13/14], 1985 August (Box 111, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1985 [14/14], 1985 August (Box 111, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1985 [1/19], 1985 November (Box 111, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting November 11-15, 1985, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk Committee, Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries), CTA Agenda
- JWAC November 1985 [2/19], 1985 November (Box 111, Folder 4)
  Minutes Meeting November 11-15, 1985, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk Committee, Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries),
- JWAC November 1985 [3/19], 1985 November (Box 111, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1985 [4/19], 1985 November (Box 111, Folder 6)
  Agenda Meeting November 11-15, 1985, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk Committee, Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1985 [5/19], 1985 November (Box 111, Folder 7)
- JWAC November 1985 [6/19], 1985 November (Box 111, Folder 8)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the CTA Grievance Committee
- JWAC November 1985 [7/19], 1985 November (Box 112, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1985 [8/19], 1985 November (Box 112, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1985 [9/19], 1985 November (Box 112, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1985 [10/19], 1985 November (Box 112, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1985 [11/19], 1985 November (Box 112, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1985 [12/19], 1985 November (Box 112, Folder 6)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Over-The-Road Committee
- JWAC November 1985 [13/19], 1985 November (Box 113, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1985 [14/19], 1985 November (Box 113, Folder 2)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk Committees
- JWAC November 1985 [15/19], 1985 November (Box 113, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1985 [16/19], 1985 November (Box 113, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1985 [17/19], 1985 November (Box 113, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1985 [18/19], 1985 November (Box 113, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1985 [19/19], 1985 November (Box 114, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1985 [1/16], 1985 November (Box 114, Folder 2)
  Agenda Meeting February 10-14, 1986, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office And Break Bulk, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1985 [2/16], 1985 November (Box 114, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1985 [3/16], 1985 November (Box 114, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1985 [4/16], 1985 November (Box 114, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1985 [5/16], 1985 November (Box 114, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1985 [6/16], 1985 November (Box 115, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts CTA Committee/Main Committee
- JWAC November 1985 [7/16], 1985 November (Box 115, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1985 [8/16], 1985 November (Box 115, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1985 [9/16], 1985 November (Box 115, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1985 [10/16], 1985 November (Box 115, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1985 [11/16], 1985 November (Box 115, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1985 [12/16], 1985 November (Box 116, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Local Operations, Office, and Break Bulk Committees
- JWAC November 1985 [13/16], 1985 November (Box 116, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1985 [14/16], 1985 November (Box 116, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1985 [15/16], 1985 November (Box 116, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1985 [16/16], 1985 November (Box 116, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1986 [1/14], 1986 May (Box 116, Folder 6)
  Agenda Meeting May 5-9, 1986, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1986 [2/14], 1986 May (Box 117, Folder 1)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting May 5-9, 1986, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1986 [3/14], 1986 May (Box 117, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1986 [4/14], 1986 May (Box 117, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1986 [5/14], 1986 May (Box 117, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1986 [6/14], 1986 May (Box 117, Folder 5)
  Proceedings/Transcripts California Trucking Association (CTA)
- JWAC May 1986 [7/14], 1986 May (Box 117, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1986 [8/14], 1986 May (Box 117, Folder 7)
- JWAC May 1986 [9/14], 1986 May (Box 118, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Local Operations, Office, and Break Bulk Committees
- JWAC May 1986 [10/14], 1986 May (Box 118, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1986 [11/14], 1986 May (Box 118, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1986 [12/14], 1986 May (Box 118, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1986 [13/14], 1986 May (Box 118, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1986 [14/14], 1986 May (Box 118, Folder 6)
- JWAC July 1986 [1/1], 1986 July (Box 118, Folder 7)
  July 1986, CTA, Maintenance of Standards, Local/Area Standards and Special Circumstances Committee
- JWAC August 1986 [1/4], 1986 August (Box 119, Folder 1)
  Agenda August 11-15, 1986, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1986 [2/4], 1986 August (Box 119, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1986 [3/4], 1986 August (Box 119, Folder 3)
  Proceedings of the California Trucking Association
- JWAC August 1986 [4/4], 1986 August (Box 119, Folder 4)
  CTA, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1986 [1/4], 1986 November (Box 119, Folder 5)
  Agenda Meeting November 10-14, 1986, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1986 [2/4], 1986 November (Box 119, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1986 [3/4], 1986 November (Box 120, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1986 [4/4], 1986 November (Box 120, Folder 2)
  Transcripts/Proceedings CTA Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC February 1987 [1/3], 1987 February (Box 120, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting February 9-13, 1987, Main Committee and Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1987 [2/3], 1987 February (Box 120, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1987 [3/3], 1987 February (Box 120, Folder 5)
  Proceedings/Transcripts CTA, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC May 1987 [1/4], 1987 May (Box 120, Folder 6)
  Agenda Meeting May 11-15, 1987, Main Committee and Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Office and Break Bulk (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1987 [2/4], 1987 May (Box 120, Folder 7)
- JWAC May 1987 [3/4], 1987 May (Box 121, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts CTA Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC May 1987 [4/4], 1987 May (Box 121, Folder 2)
  Proceedings/Transcripts CTA Committee
- JWAC August 1987 [1/3], 1987 August (Box 121, Folder 3)
  Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1987 [2/3], 1987 August (Box 121, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1987 [3/3], 1987 August (Box 121, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1987 [1/1], 1987 November (Box 121, Folder 6)
  Agenda Meeting November 9-13, 1987, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1988 [1/2], 1988 February (Box 121, Folder 7)
  Agenda Meeting February 8-12, 1988, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1988 [2/2], 1988 February (Box 122, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1988 [1/2], 1988 May (Box 122, Folder 2)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting May 9-13, 1988, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1988 [2/2], 1988 May (Box 122, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1988 [1/2], 1988 August (Box 122, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting August 15-19, 1988, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1988 [2/2], 1988 August (Box 122, Folder 5)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the CTA
- JWAC November 1988 [1/2], 1988 November (Box 122, Folder 6)
  Agenda, Minutes, Meeting November 14-18, 1988, Main Committee, O-T-R and Automotive Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1988 [2/2], 1988 November (Box 122, Folder 7)
- JWAC February 1989 [1/2], 1989 February (Box 123, Folder 1)
  Minutes, Agenda Meeting February 13-17, 1989, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1989 [2/2], 1989 February (Box 123, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1989 [1/3], 1989 May (Box 123, Folder 3)
  Agenda, Minutes, Meeting May 15-19, 1989, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1989 [2/3], 1989 May (Box 123, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1989 [3/3], 1989 May (Box 123, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1989 [3/3], 1989 May (Box 123, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1989 [1/3], 1989 August (Box 123, Folder 6)
  Agenda, Minutes, Meeting August 14-18, 1989, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations, Over-The-Road Cases, Yellow Freight Cases (Summaries)